{
    "subject": "resource/184th_Pennsylvania_Infantry",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/Union_(American_Civil_War)",
    "human_readable": "The 184th Pennsylvania Infantry is from the Union.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.985202968120575,
            "question": "To which union did the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9834356904029846,
            "question": "Was the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry part of the Union or the Confederacy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8832602500915527,
            "question": "What was the military affiliation of the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8481168150901794,
            "question": "Who were the opponents of the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8176022171974182,
            "question": "Which historical conflict involved the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7855057120323181,
            "question": "What was the political affiliation of the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7485257983207703,
            "question": "What side was the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry on during the Civil War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7195407152175903,
            "question": "What was the allegiance of the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6533088684082031,
            "question": "In what war did the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry fight?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03281211480498314,
            "question": "Which side were they fighting for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The 184th Pennsylvania Infantry is from the Union.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3047_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what war did the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry fight?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3047_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the allegiance of the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3047_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What side was the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry on during the Civil War?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3047_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3047_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3047_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3047_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3047_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3047_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3047_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3047_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3047_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3047_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3047_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The first document mentions the \"UNION PENNSYLVANIA VOLUNTEERS\" and the 184th Regiment, Pennsylvania Infantry, which suggests that it is part of the Union army."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided mentions \"184th Regiment, Pennsylvania Infantry,\" which indicates that this unit was indeed part of the Union Army during the American Civil War. Therefore, the statement \"The 184th Pennsylvania Infantry is from the Union\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}